One dream,
one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
This battle that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, they
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marked maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead to new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
Century!
You fight and leave Otako to me!
Thanks, Usuhachi!
Good luck with that dinosaur, buddy!
No problem.
I'll wrap this up quick!
Two-sword style.
Tower Prime return!
Try some Diablo Jolet!
CONCETE!
Damn, he's strong!
Did you guys see that?
Hate to say it, but that guy might
be an even match for the boss!
Quit while you're ahead, Ronin.
Who is this guy?
And now it's too late!
Seems like fortune favors me today.
There's no way he can
handle the Oniwa Banshu too!
It's just as Hawkins reported.
All of the Straw Hats have somehow
wormed their way into the land of Wano.
All we need is one of you.
I don't care who it is.
Your capture and subsequent
torture will reveal your purpose.
Capture them!
That's some kind of magic?
Ninpo.
Help Biwa!
You cheater! It's just a gun!
Dock!
Worry not, fair maiden!
You need only flee the capital.
Leave these ruffians to me.
I'll teach them the true
meaning of rock and roll.
Cause I'm the Soul King! Baby!
I call this one Akashatokuro!
Who is that woman?
She was speaking with Zoro Judo.
Before she took off running, Fujin
rajin—see where that woman is heading?
I knew
you'd
make your
appearance soon enough.
Hello, Trafalgar Law,
you came to save us!
I'm sorry, captain, we screwed up
the plan for everyone, didn't we?
I noticed that our polar
bears and with them with
your ability you could get
them out in an instant.
What kind of fool would keep all
their valuable hostages in one place,
let alone such a conspicuous one?
Rather, you're about to
become a hostage yourself.
Oh yeah, how's that?
Didn't you learn anything?
The last time—did you learn anything?
You can't
lay a finger on me, not anymore!
not anymore
If you want to win, there are
four lives you must extinguish.
The fourth life would
be my own, of course.
But the other three before
me are your own crewmates.
That's better.
You understand now.
Try some Diablo shelter!
On the city!
I would expect nothing less of a Vinsmoke.
Didn't hear me the last time?
Don't ever speak that name to me again!
That was you in the Silver
Mouse costume, wasn't it?
I'll never tell why the hell
am I so popular with dino men
Keep at this and I'll cut
your tail off and grill it up.
Let me warn you.
I'm a lot tougher than page one
It's more fun to improve
the flavor of crappy meat
I know that sound.
It's a beautiful woman,
and she needs my help.
Diablo-jamba!
Extra hot cheese hash!
Oh,
my
God.
I can't keep a lady waiting.
Never fear, my dear.
I'm on the way.
You're protecting her.
You're supposed to be hiding
so you won't get hurt.
I tried to hide.
I must have drawn
attention when I ran away.
Mosshead knows that woman.
That beautiful woman?!
Your bounty isn't even as high
as mine, you arrogant bastard!
You need to learn your place!
Don't do this!
I choose not to join you and
you decide to destroy my life?!
Please, Ashura!
We didn't want that at all!
My intention was to turn our
enemy into yours as well.
I created a conflict, hoping it would
motivate you to change your ways.
And yet, I harmed you, my friend.
I should have come to you on
hands and knees as I am now,
instead of engaging in deception.
Spurred by the urgency of our battle,
I justified my actions by
invoking the name of Lord Odin,
but I was mistaken from the very start.
Because it was but a moment to me, I failed
to understand the weight of 20 years.
The minds of this country's
people have changed.
It is a truth that I failed to see.
No, that I selfishly refused to see.
And yet there were many
hearts that did not change.
Unshakable beliefs that weathered
the cruel passage of time.
Lord Yasui revealed this
truth to me in the end.
Thanks to his courage,
our plan may yet succeed.
And although Lord Yasui has been lost.
He has shattered the enemy's hold over us.
I have faith that the samurai captured
by Orochi will not be deterred,
but rather emboldened.
They will understand why Lord Yasui lied.
The crescent moon symbol has
not lost its meaning to them.
Soon they will be free, and I am
certain they will join us in our battle.
On the night of the fire festival,
we will go forth and raid Onigashima.
We have not been defeated in the least.
And yet,
if we hope to see this through to the
end, to the death of Kaido and Orochi,
we need your help!
Will you please fight
beside us once more, Ashura?
Follow me.
There's something important
I think you need to see.
I know it's in there!
My sweet red bean soap!
She did it!
Aline, you're so strong!
And we are so dead!
What was that?
We are under attack!
The front gate has been
completely destroyed!
Impossible!
Whoever did that has a death wish.
Someone go kick their ass! Bring it on!
You're not taking another stab!
Hope you're ready to die!
Face sounds quite powerful!
The intruder has successfully
broken through the second gate!
They're now approaching the third gate!
Stop them, dammit!
The third gate is...
What the hell?
What is that?
It's Big Mom!
I gotta be seeing things!
This can't be real!
It's really her!
That's Big Mom!
Big what?
Is that something yummy?
I thought she got knocked
to the bottom of the sea!
What the hell is she
doing here in my prison?!
Oh, I'm so hungry.
This is insanity.
What kind of monster can
destroy a steel gate?
She's too dangerous.
We need to fall back.
She's on the same level as Kaido.
They're both emperors.
But why is she here?
Surely she didn't come
here to start a war!
Smells yummy!
It must be close.
Red bean soup!
Wait, soup?
Otama, hurry!
The red bean soup is here!
I can smell it!
Help me find some!
Did you guys hear that?
Olita's colony!
Come on in!
We can eat it together!
Wait, what?
You mean they actually have it?
In here, I thought I was going to
pay for that stupid lie with my life!
More than that, she smashed
through the gate like nothing.
Frankly, I wasn't certain
we could get inside.
It was easier than I thought.
Okie Dock, now we just have to
get in there and rescue Big Bro!
Come on, Momo, we have to hurry!
Of course.
After all, Luffy's counting
on us, right? I forbid it.
Otama, you and Lord Momonosuke must hide
from the enemy and wait outside. What?
Why can't we come too?
Make no mistake, it's incredibly
dangerous inside of those walls.
And in the case of Lord Momonosuke, his
very existence must be kept a secret.
Right you are.
But Okiku, you shouldn't let them
know that you're alive either.
Oh, a fine point.
Very well, I'll fashion a disguise.
This should serve quite nicely.
Perfect.
I'm concealed.
This has rendered me both discreet
and anonymous. I am ready.
You summoned!
I really have a lot of faith in those
claw face things for some reason!
A brief warning first.
Udon is ruled by Queen.
He is one of the strongest members of
the Beast Pirates, a lead performer.
Let's be cautious and stay alert.
What did you just say?
You hag!
I'm not giving my food to you!
I hope so!
I came a long way!
Poor Tommy.
It won't be long now.
You helped me, right?
I heard there's a whole
bunch of red bean soup here.
You wouldn't mind sharing, I'm sure.
Is that a joke?
I ain't sharing a damn
bite with your wrinkly ass.
And who the hell told you I had Oshiruko?
What is this?
You trying to start a fight
moving in on my favorite snack?
Hey, stop arguing, or at least
pull them out of the stupid water.
You're here running your
mouth about some stupid beans,
and two people are about to die.
You think my soup is stupid.
Here it comes—he's losing
it; we're all gonna die.
He's
so angry; he's transforming—that
soup is what keeps me alive.
No one
can take it away from me.
He means
it—he's really gonna fight
with her master queen!
Please control yourself, getting.
control yourself getting Getting into a
fight with Big Mom over food is suicide!
This will not end well!
It's over!
There's no stopping him now!
I don't know what that deafening roar
was, but it didn't sound like Olene to me.
So scary.
Neither of them will be
happy when they see this.
We're finished.
We can't make a second batch.
There's no time
You're right, we have a ton of Oshiroko
here, but it belongs to me alone.
I won't share a drop with you
Oh, I see now
Polina's still pretty scary, but
she's like a nice version of Big Mom,
so I don't know if she can
stand up to Queen or not.
Wow, this is weird.
I'm almost worried about her.
So what I'm hearing is that
you've got Oshiruko, right?
Listen, woman.
I will fight you to the death before
I even let you look at my Oshiruko.
Now buzz off or die!
Karoo!
Uh...
Whoa!
What the...
Listen, you...
I came for that soup, OK?
And I will have it!
Olene!
Let the queen know!
CastingWords